It's safe to say Venice is
free of Hitman from the Family.
We're in the clear.
Let's head to the airport now.
We're taking to the skies.
That'll get us to our next destination.
We are headed for the Isle of Sardinia.
If we're to succeed, it's imperative
that we uncover the boss's past.
Our lives depend on it.
I'm not picking up any foreign life forms.
We should be good to go.
There's not even so much as a
cockroach on board this plane.
That's good, because it's ours now.
You're to keep everything away from
this plane, living or otherwise.
Once we take off,
we'll be flying at nearly
800 kilometers an hour,
and at an altitude of
several thousand meters.
Luckily for us, it'd be impossible
for a user to give chase.
A Stan couldn't keep up with
us at that height and speed.
So, you ready?
Sardinia is waiting for us.
Our total flight time
will be about two hours.
Let's go.
Don't care.
Chishinya don't need a Nunzio.
Hear da honobiru Diego.
I nori wokie. Help you! Hell no!
Hachimari no gobelin!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
This thing don't you
think that's dangerous
how do you even know for
sure the last trip the
captain took was to
Sardinia there's this thing
called INS apparently
you put your destination
in the plane's computer
and it automatically
takes you there saw it in
a movie once i find the
INS and enter our
destination we'll be good to
go you're basing your plan on
a movie well Well, Abacchio,
how much longer until
we take off? Not sure.
That's one thing I can't fast-forward.
Maybe ten minutes or so.
Bucciarati's leg.
I'm pretty sure he badly
injured it in the last battle.
How could a gash that
deep not be gushing blood?
Ahead to the left!
We've got company coming!
It's getting closer! Mista!
Hey!
Stay right where you are!
Don't take this the wrong way!
I'm sure you're a perfectly nice guy,
but if you keep skulking around this
plane, I'll have to gun your ass down!
Though,
the way your creeper ass is
still lumbering toward us,
I'm starting to get the feeling you
might not be that nice of a guy.
So let me be clear, get lost or get dead!
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt
and assume your ears were all clogged up.
Well, unclog and get this through your
skull, because I won't say it again.
Walk away, or I start painting
the runway with your plot.
He's a stand user!
Six bullets!
Yahoo! Woo-hoo!
Giorno! Narancia!
We've got another enemy on our hands!
The signal disappeared.
Looks like he was the only one.
I don't currently see
anyone else near our plane.
Forget it, Giorno.
That Katsone's history.
Just leave him be.
We need to go.
Yes, I know that.
But we can't be too careful.
Don't you think that was too easy?
It's almost as if he
wanted you to shoot him.
Hey, what's with all that?
Was that a dig at me and six bullets?
Getting jealous of our
skills isn't a good look.
Fact is, he sucks and we don't.
You're goddamn right!
There's no question that he's dead.
He's not breathing.
There's no pulse.
And his life energy's vanished.
Mista! Giorno!
We're about to take off!
Get over here!
Our ride's calling.
I wonder if my father, rather...
I wonder if your boss ever thought I'd
travel to Sardinia to
uncover his hidden past.
Former boss.
We're done.
With him and his madness.
Insofar as his machinations go, he shrewd.
Assuming he's predicted our plan,
this info's even more vital.
I suspect that at the time he
met your mother in Sardinia,
he wasn't yet a mafioso in hiding.
No, he was most likely
just an ordinary young man.
He joined the mafia sometime later,
which means something
from his previous life
will tell us who the boss
really was 15 years ago.
And you are the best person to
find that something. Think back.
Anything can help.
Can you think of any
stories from your childhood?
Maybe some your mother used to tell you?
Kill di Volpe. There.
Kill di Volpe?
The Bay of the Fox?
That's right.
It's a rather famous resort
on the costa Smeralda.
She said that's how the two of them
met, while she was on vacation.
She also told me that my
father grew up in Sardinia.
Apparently, he spoke
with a Sardinian dialect.
Then he just up and vanished.
Mom never found out anything else
about him, not even his name.
That's everything I know.
Beyond that, I'm at a loss.
And besides, it's just
my mom's reminiscing.
You are the only living
relative the boss has left.
You threaten his precious anonymity,
which is why he's fighting to end you.
Squalo di Volpe, huh?
That is the name of our first actual lead.
Mista You might want to
start getting your gun ready.
Just take a listen to this sound!
What sound?
Are you talking about the engine?
You're not making sense.
Trust me, just get out your gun!
It's in the cabinet.
Hey, hey, hey, hey?
I don't know what it is,
but something's up with you.
Before we got on, didn't you say there
wasn't even a cockroach on this damn thing?
Yeah, I did.
And I'm still not picking up
on any life force on board.
But...
But what, Giorno?
Are you trying to tell me we have
a long-distance stand on board?
You sure you're not just a
little loose in the noodle?
Well, yeah, I suppose
that's a possibility.
But I'm sure.
I heard something concerning.
I'm opening the cabinet, which
is why I need your gun ready.
A freezer?
Forgive me, Mista.
I guess my nerves simply
got the better of me there.
Chorno, what the hell
kind of joke is this?
Wouldn't you have time to
put that in the freezer?
What?
Were you trying to scare me with those
crusty chicken scraps or something?
Whatever.
Your sense of humor sucks to high heaven.
That's not chicken at all.
There is blood, though.
It looks like it's still fresh, too.
Wait a minute.
Aren't those the fingers of that mozzarella
ball I knocked off back at the airport?
Giorno, tell me I'm wrong!
Hey, just calm down, Mista.
Look at that.
There's another one in there now.
What is it?
Something I should know?
Giorno, when we came aboard this aircraft,
you were positive that it
was devoid of any life.
But now Mista is saying he witnessed
three severed fingers multiply to four.
How is this happening?
Are they not giving off any energy at all?
They're inanimate.
No life whatsoever.
If they were just animate,
or even if they were
some sort of new stand,
Golden Wind's power simply wouldn't work.
Plant life would never sprout from them.
Look, you guys, I know those multiplying
zombie digits really spooked me out,
but let's be real, shall we?
I was probably just seeing things.
Even so, why are these stupid freaking
fingers on this stupid freaking plane?
That's what I'd like to know.
Someone planted these here, but
the how and who elude us for now.
Regardless, they have to go. What?
You don't mean off the plane, do you?
But you can't open the
door while we're airborne.
We'll get sucked out like turds
being flung down the toilet.
Hold on tight to something.
Open her up, Zipperman!
Well, the job is finished
and with nary a soul flung.
Make sure there are no more.
Check every crevice of this plane.
Yeah I could go for some pizza too nothing
complicated just a pizza
margarita from Napoli
What the heck is this
a train station stall
what's with the graffiti
isn't this some rich
guy's plane?
What the hell is going on here?
The name of that guy's stand is
Notorious chase who in the hell wrote
this and when what would the Stan
have to gain by doing this what
These fingers no it can't be
Bucciarati just threw them
outside we didn't touch Is
this what wrote the graffiti?
Is it a corpse?
Impossible!
Its user is dead!
So the stand has to be too!
Merida!
It's fading on my body and getting bigger!
Golden wind!
Pack off my right arm fast!
Wait! What in the hell?
It looks exactly like my hand!
Shit!
It's devouring my stand!
The one who wrote that
graffiti on the wall?
He brought those fingers aboard!
It was me.
What's the problem, Giorno?
Hey, you good?
Golden wind.
Yahoo!
Hey, Giorno.
You better start making a replacement arm!
And quickly.
What the hell?
Did he just try to pounce
on Golden Wind's arm?
What's going on, Giorno?
This is madness!
Forget everything you know about stands.
We've never seen this before.
If that aberration is a stand, then
its user has to be hiding somewhere.
He's not here.
We already killed him.
Back there on the runway.
I knew there was something
weird about the guy.
He approached us so he could die and let
his stand hunt us down from the skies.
His essence lives on.
It seems being killed triggered
the emergence of his stand.
It has no user, so it can keep up
without being tethered to a person.
Don't you worry.
It's as slow as a slug.
Actually, since it's not
moving, you think it's dead.
Has to be.
After being blasted, it's not moving.
No. No. Run. Shot.
It's It's feeding, it
doesn't need to move.
I got too close.
This bastard is quick.
Damn thing got my bullets.
It got four of them, more than half.
Number two, three, six, seven.
It's deadly, damn it.
You have to stay away.
Get back, all of you. Mista.
Not good, stay back.
What's going on?
Why is it going after Narancia?
It's got to have some method
of discerning its next victim.
Don't you think I'm scared of you?
All I gotta do is keep my distance?
Well then, nice thing is I don't have
to get close to fill you full of holes.
That movement, so I was right.
It is detecting something.
Damn it!
It's so fast!
I can't keep up with that speed!
At this rate, that meat monster of
a stand is gonna slaughter us all!
Narancia! Quick, Trish!
Hide in the closet and stay quiet!
What oh no what's it one with
Trish get it and shut the door?
I understand I know what it's tracking
it's movement moving objects trigger it?
to zero in for the kill.
That explains how it's choosing us.
The more swiftly its target moves,
the more voraciously it seeks
to consume its panicking prey.
If we can just get this thing off my
left arm, we can all make it to Sardinia.
It's our only option now.
It'll be like this never happened.
Just wait, Giorno!
No!
You use your stand to recover injuries!
You can't do that if you lose both arms!
Make it latch onto me!
I'll deal with it myself! Hurry!
We're out of time, Bucciarati!
It's starting to creep up my arm!
No!
Don't do it!
No, Jean!
We were so close.
Sardinia was within reach.
Mista and Narancia are…
This isn't happening.
All this happened because of me.
Because I decided to bring
my team onto this plane.
I ignored every single pitfall.
This is my mistake to own.
No one could have
anticipated this. No one.
Being on this plane
granted us the opportunity
to rid ourselves of that stand for good.
We have to do something
about their injuries.
They're serious.
They can start recovering in the turtle.
Hang on, about their injuries.
I need you to tell me the truth.
His arms, they can be replaced.
Isn't that right?
His stand, Golden Wind,
has the power to do that?
Golden Wind and Zipperman
can only actuate their powers
through direct contact
with their hands and fists.
Neither of us have ever suffered
damage like this before.
Giorno Giovanna is out of commission.
Which means, so are Mista and Arantxa.
Giorno has no way of
regenerating his arms.
Trish, you should get some rest.
I'll bring a Bacchio up to
speed on what's happened.
I'm...
I'm traveling to Sardinia
for my own benefit.
For me, and me alone.
All of this bloodshed due to me
wanting to learn about my father.
Only because it serves my interests.
But Giorno and the others are different.
They're not concerned
about their own safety.
They're fighting for what they
believe is right and just.
As I am.
I don't think I could ever do that.
Was that a ball?
Why is a ball out there?
What in the world?
How the hell was it not sent
flying from the airplane?
Wait, of course it didn't fly away.
Journal.
It's movement.
Moving objects trigger it
to zero in for the kill.
That explains how it's choosing us.
We're flying through
the air at a high speed.
It's drawn to whatever
object is moving fastest.
That would certainly explain
why it went after the knife.
I've got to get into the
closet and shut the door now.
Slowly, I have to move slowly.
Slow but with purpose.
I can detect anything.
Why'd it change direction all of a sudden?
Something must have set it off.
That's Giorno's brooch?
C-could it be alive?
Golden wind is transforming.
Is it turning into Giorno's arms?
His left hand.
I can't believe it.
It's forming a brand new hand!
Before he severed his arm,
Giorno had already begun
growing a replacement.
by infusing the ladybug
with life-giving energy.
Giorno's not going down
without a hell of a fight!
As long as I keep that
thing away from his hand,
Narancia and Mista might have a chance!
But how the hell do I do that?
They were accusing.
They've always been knowing.
What is just fiction?
Or what is the truth?
They have a mission.
They are the question.
But they dare to tell us.
What's bad and what's good?
Stand up!
Join us!
Come on!
Just say this!
We are the power!
We'll see the future!
As we are fighters!
Just fighting for a ride.
Thank you.